<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Recipes</string>
    <string name="str_choose">Choose available ingredients:</string>
    <string name="str_head">Welcome to MobCook!</string>
    <string name="str_done">Search</string>
    <string name="str_title">TITLE</string>
    <string name="str_ingredients">Ingredients:</string>
    <string name="str_tutorial">tutorial tutorial tutorial tutorial tutorial tutorial tutorial tutorial</string>
    <string name="str_arugula">Arugula</string>
    <string name="str_apple">Apple</string>
    <string name="str_bacon">Bacon</string>
    <string name="str_beans">Beans</string>
    <string name="str_bread">Bread</string>
    <string name="str_butter">Butter</string>
    <string name="str_cinnamon">Cinnamon</string>
    <string name="str_chickenBreasts">Chicken breasts</string>
    <string name="str_egg">Egg</string>
    <string name="str_fetaCheese">Feta cheese</string>
    <string name="str_garlic">Garlic</string>
    <string name="str_lemon">Lemon</string>
    <string name="str_onion">Onion</string>
    <string name="str_potato">Potato</string>
    <string name="str_swissChard">Swiss chard</string>

    <string name="tutorialPuree">Put the potatoes, whole, in a pot and cover with cold water. Salt the water. Bring to
        a boil, and simmer until very tender, about 30 minutes, depending on size.
    Meanwhile, drop the garlic, bay leaf, and thyme in a saucepan with the milk, bring to a boil, turn off the heat,
        cover, and set aside to infuse 10 minutes. Pull out the garlic and herbs, and discard.
    When the potatoes are done, drain them and peel while hot. Put them through a food mill set on the smallest
        setting over a large pot. Beat in the butter a piece at a time. Bring the milk to a boil and beat it in, splash
        by splash, until completely absorbed. You are looking for a very soft, fine puree, not unlike baby food! Check
        the seasonings, and serve.</string>

    <string name="tutorialBakedPecorinoChicken">5 slices sandwich bread.
    1/2cup grated pecorino (2 ounces).
    2tablespoons unsalted butter, melted.
    Kosher salt and black pepper.
    4 6-ounce boneless, skinless chicken breasts.
    1tablespoon olive oil.
    2 bunches Swiss chard, stems discarded and leaves cut into 1-inch strips Heat oven to 400° F. In a food processor,
    pulse the bread until coarse crumbs form (you should have about 2 cups). Add the pecorino, butter, ½ teaspoon salt,
        and ¼ teaspoon pepper and pulse once or twice to moisten.
    Place the chicken in an 8-inch baking dish; season with ½ teaspoon salt and ¼ teaspoon pepper and sprinkle with the
        bread crumb mixture. Cover with foil and bake until cooked through, 15 to 20 minutes. Uncover and bake until
        crumbs are golden, 3 to 5 minutes.
    Meanwhile, heat the oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat. Add the chard, ½ teaspoon salt, and ¼ teaspoon
        pepper. Cook, tossing, until tender, 3 to 4 minutes. Serve with the chicken.</string>

    <string name="tutorialRocketbeans">4 slices bacon, sliced crosswise into 1/2-inch pieces 1 tablespoon olive oil 1
        (15 ounce) jar butter
        beans, drained and rinsed 1 pinch salt and freshly ground black pepper to taste 3 cloves garlic, minced 2 cups
        arugula, coarsely chopped 1/2 lemon, juiced. Cook bacon in olive oil in a large skillet over medium heat until
        crisp, about 8 minutes. Pour butter beans into bacon and drippings; toss lightly. Season with salt and black
        pepper; cook 3 more minutes to blend flavors.
        Stir garlic into beans and cook just until fragrant, about 30 seconds. Toss arugula into mixture and cook until
        wilted; remove from heat. Stir in lemon juice.</string>

    <string name="tutorialBaconFetaBeans">8 slices bacon - cooked, crumbled and divided 1 (16 ounce) package frozen cut
        green beans 1 teaspoon minced garlic 4 ounces crumbled feta cheese, divided 1/2 teaspoon onion powder 1/8
        teaspoon ground black pepper 2 tablespoons water. Place bacon in a large, deep skillet. Cook over medium
        high heat until evenly browned but only slightly crisp. Drain grease, leaving a small amount in the skillet
        for later use. Crumble bacon, reserving 2 tablespoons for garnish, and set aside.
        Cook frozen beans in a covered, microwavable dish for about 3 minutes until thawed, but not fully cooked.
        Drain liquid, pat dry, and set aside.
        Reheat skillet with residual bacon grease over medium-high heat. Stir in bacon and garlic until garlic is
        lightly golden. Add green beans and feta cheese, and season with onion powder and black pepper. Cook and
        stir until most of the feta cheese has melted, about 2 minutes. Transfer to a serving dish, and garnish with
        remaining feta cheese and crumbled bacon. Serve hot.</string>

    <string name="tutorialPotatoPancakes">1 cup cold water 1 egg, beaten 1/2 teaspoon salt 3/4 cup dry potato flakes 1
        tablespoon chopped chives 1 pinch freshly ground black pepper 1 pinch cayenne pepper, or to taste 1 tablespoon
        vegetable oil 1 tablespoon butter 1/4 cup sour cream for garnish 1 tablespoon chopped chives, divided.
        Whisk together water, egg and salt in a large bowl until salt has dissolved. Stir in dry potato flakes until
        incorporated. Stir in 1 tablespoon of chopped chives; season with black pepper and cayenne pepper. Heat oil
        and butter in a large skillet over medium-high heat. Swirl the pan to combine. Divide potato mixture into four
        equal portions and shape into pancakes. Place the pancakes in the pan and reduce heat to medium. Cook until a
        well-browned crust has formed onto the bottom of the pancakes, about 10 minutes. Flip each pancake and flatten
        slightly. Cook until other sides are browned, 7 to 8 more minutes. Transfer to plate; top each pancake with a
        dollop of sour cream and sprinkle each with 3/4 teaspoon chives.</string>

    <string name="tutorialApplesauce">4 apples - peeled, cored and chopped 3/4 cup water 1/4 cup white sugar 1/2
        teaspoon ground cinnamon. In a saucepan, combine apples, water, sugar, and cinnamon. Cover, and cook over
        medium heat for 15 to 20 minutes, or until apples are soft. Allow to cool, then mash with a fork or potato
        masher.</string>

    <string name="tutorialSauteedApples">1/4 cup butter 4 large tart apples - peeled, cored and sliced 1/4 inch thick 2
        teaspoons cornstarch 1/2 cup cold water 1/2 cup brown sugar 1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon. In a large skillet or
        saucepan, melt butter over medium heat; add apples. Cook, stirring constantly, until apples are almost tender,
        about 6 to 7 minutes. Dissolve cornstarch in water; add to skillet. Stir in brown sugar and cinnamon. Boil for
        2 minutes, stirring occasionally. Remove from heat and serve warm.</string>

    <string name="tutorialFriedEggs">1) For Over-Easy or Over-Hard Eggs: HEAT 2 tsp. butter in nonstick skillet over
        medium-high heat until hot. 2) BREAK eggs and SLIP into pan, 1 at a time. IMMEDIATELY reduce heat to
        low. 3) COOK SLOWLY until whites are completely set and yolks begin to thicken but are not hard. SLIDE turner
        under each egg and carefully FLIP it over in pan. COOK second side to desired doneness. SPRINKLE with salt and
        pepper. SERVE immediately.</string>

</resources>
